{
    "id": "0ec5f20ea1674458a2c36362246dc4b3",
    "title": "As, Like, As If",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "282fbd3f92d74b9bb66f2e34e6c54dde",
            "title": "As, Like, As If",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She works .............................. a waitress.",
                    "description": "As can be used to say what role a person or thing has.",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ran ................................. wind.",
                    "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... you know, we have to improve our productivity.",
                    "description": "This is a common expression beginning with as.",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Like",
                        "As if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She walks ..................................... a duck.",
                    "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don't cry .................................... a baby.",
                    "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I felt ..................................... laughing.",
                    "description": "I felt like laughing means I wanted to laugh.",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. a child, I used to be afraid of spiders.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Like",
                        "As if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It looks .................................. a cat.",
                    "description": "Like is a preposition. It is followed by a noun/pronoun which acts as its object. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It looks ................................... it is going to rain.",
                    "description": "As if is used to say what a situation seems like. Like is possible here in a careless style. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She talks .................................... she knew everything.",
                    "description": "As if is used to say what a situation seems like.",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He sat there smiling .................................... he had won a jackpot.",
                    "description": "As if is used to say what a situation seems like.",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He fought ...................................... a lion.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}